Guide to the Carl Feiss papers, [ca.1928]-1991
Feiss, Carl papers, [ca.1928]-1991
- Series II. Professional Papers
  - Oversize Materials
    - Raleigh, North Carolina: correspondence, Heritage Square plans, "Fifth and Sixth Reports of the Commission on Reorganization of State Government, Heritage Square State Capital Planning Commission," clippings, "Planning Program: State Governmental Center and Heritage Square," "Summary Status Report: State Capital Planning and Heritage Square Project," "Projected Personnel and Space Needs for Priority Group," maps, meeting minutes, "Outline of the Comprehensive Report of the Central Business District of Durham.", 1964 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Raleigh, North Carolina: city plan, "Proposal for a Study of the Space Use Relationships Between the State Government and the CBD (Central Business District)," "Current Space Use of State Buildings," "State Buildings?Qualitative Analysis," "Buildings of Historical and Architectural Significance in the Capitol Square Area," "Summary of Business Establishments in CBD Core and Fringe," "Preliminary Analysis and Findings: 1) Interaction of State Employees and the CBD 2) CBD Space Projections," "North Carolina's State Legislative Building," "Projection of CBD Core and Fringe Space Needs for Selected Business Establishments, "Total Square Feet of Floor Area: State Buildings," "Automobile Parking Requirements for State Employees and Visitors," "Requirements for Floor and Parking Space by Priority Group in Areas," "Projected Personnel and Space Needs by Priority Group," "Land Requirements 1970-2000 Based on Density Ration.", 1963 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Rookery Bay Sanctuary: Naples, Florida: "Water Control," correspondence, Florida laws, "School Facilities," "Parks and Playgrounds," correspondence, "An Analysis of Urban Development Potential Near Rookery Bay Sanctuary.", 1965-1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Savannah, Georgia: Historic Savannah Foundation: Newsletter, July 1, 1975; correspondence; "An Ordinance to establish the historic zone: to provide regulations therein: to repeal all conflicting ordinances and for other purposes; "Urban Renewal Plan: Central Urban Renewal Area Project 1;" South Carolina State Gazette, January 1971., 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Savannah, Georgia: Historic Savannah Foundation: clippings., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: "Proposed Work Elements of Annual Work Program," "River Basin work schedule," "Land Use Study Outline," "Population Study," "Housing Market Analysis: Scope and Methodology," "Land Use Study Methodology," "Approach and Purpose," clippings, meeting agenda, "Land Use Ordinance," "A Preliminary Investigation of the Use of the Natural Resources in the Tampa Bay Region as a Basis for Future Development Policy," "Project Flowchart and Schedule: Resource Management Study," status report, brochure for Florida Power Corp., "Project Description and Scope," organizational tree, correspondence, memoranda, contract between Feiss and Tampa Bay Regional Council., 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: "Schedule for Preparing Tellico Newtown Planning Report," "Democracy in New Towns: The Limits of Private Government," notes, maps, chart., 1970 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, "Dock Board/Bechtel Report Presentation," "Forecast of General Cargo Foreign Trade in the Port of New Orleans," press release, "Bureau of Governmental Research Position Paper on the Vieux Carre Demonstration Study," "Secretary Volpe Rejects Riverfront Expressway in New Orleans.", 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "Petition for a Declaratory Judgement that Construction of Elevated Expressway Through the Vieux Carre Section of the City of New Orleans is Unconstitutional and Alternatively, That Vieux Carre Preservation Legislation is Unconstitutional.", 1967 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Oversize Materials, Oversize Reference Materials
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, list of members of Louisiana Council for the Vieux Carre, summary reports, plans., 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: clippings., 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Columbia, South Carolina: "In Step With Tomorrow.", 1961 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Defense, National: "Defense of the Hampton Roads.", 1941 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Feiss Family: "The Feiss Collection: An Exhibition of books from the library of Paul L. Feiss in the Kent State University Libraries," "The Joseph & Feiss Co?. in War and in Peace.", 1975, ? (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Innovative Projects Review, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - International Planning: Columbia: Stanley Crescent #352 Brookwood Drive, Wright City, Columbia., 1959 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - International Planning: Germany: "Das Osterrichische Fertighaus.", 1953 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - International Planning: India: "Preliminary Outline for Village Planning and Reconstruction.", 1946 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - International Planning: Mexico: Architectos de Mexico 30, Calli 9., 1968 (Box 40a, Folder 1)
    - Kingsmill: Busch Properties: maps and blueprints (Box 40a, Folder 2)
    - New Orleans: "New Orleans in Action: Capital Budget 1963." (Box 40a, Folder 2)
    - Shopping Centers, 1947 (Box 40a, Folder 3)
    - Virgin Islands: "Virgin Islands Community Renewal Program.", 1965 (Box 40a, Folder 4)
    - Zoning Ordinances, 1930-1946 (Box 40a, Folder 5)
  - Reference Materials
    - Action, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture: Department of Agriculture: Community Resource Development Newsletter, Community Development Districts., 1966-1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture: Department of Agriculture: Annual Report on Joint DA and HUD Programs for Non-Metropolitan Planning and Development Districts., 1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture: Department of Agriculture: Orville Freeman., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture: Agricultural Planning., 1942-1945 (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
    - America the Beautiful Fund, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - America the Beautiful Fund, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Architects: Legislative Committee, Federal Agencies Committee: "Proposal for a Commitment to an Effective Government Relations Program.", 1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - American Labor Party: News Sheet., 1939 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - American Society of Planning Officials: "Office for Emergency Management.", 1941 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Authorities: "Valley Authorities: Shall We Establish Regional Developments?" "The ?Authority' Issue.", 1945 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Arkansas: "Arkansas National Policy Statement.", 1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Aviation, 1941-1945 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
    - Bratenahl Place, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Bridgeport, Connecticut: "Housing in the Greater Bridgeport Region.", 1960 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Brookings Institution: John Shilvey., 1969 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Brookings Institution: "Transportation Needs and Resources.", 1955 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Business District Plans: "An Invitation to Industry: Saint Paul," "Patterns and Recent Trends of Chicago's Outlying Business Centers," "Business Districts," "Downtown Saint Paul: A Plan for Its Development.", 1942-1945 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Chicago: "Segments of the Past.", 1962 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Civil Service, 1942 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Clearwater Historical Inventory, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Cleveland, Ohio: "Shopping Centers," "Places to Live.", 1948 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Coalition for Bigger Cities: clippings from The New York Times., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - CONSAD Research Corp.: Dr. T.R. Lakshmanan, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Conservation: Forest, Water Resources: "Conservation," "Saving Our Soil," "Forested Lands," "Range Lands," "Land Tenures," "Land Values," "Water and Our Forests," Water Conservation Conference Continuing Committee Newsletter., 1937-1946 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Denver, Colorado: "The Valley Highway: A North-South Limited-Access Highway Through Denver.", 1944 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Denver, Colorado: "A New Way to Paul Klee," "Guide to the Fine Arts in Denver," "Denver Municipal Yearbook 1944," "Denver Municipal Yearbook 1943," "First Denver Congress on Air Age Education.", 1943-1947 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Denver Colorado: The Denver Planning Commission: "City and County Building.", 1943 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Department of the Interior: National Register, 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Department of the Interior: Bureau of Outdoor Recreation., 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 33-34)
    - Earlham College Contribution to Community Development: "The Community Dynamics Experiment.", 1960 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Engineers, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Environic Foundation International (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Federal Works Agency, 1941-1942, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Finch, Herbert, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Florida: "The Value of the Tidal Marsh.", 1973 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Florida: "A Statement to Reubin O'D. Askew," clippings, Salla Com, " Florida Growth Policy: Some Underlying Questions.", 1973 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Florida: "Migration Into Florida.", 1973 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Grand Coolee Project: "Its Story in Pictures.", 1941 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Greenbelt Towns: "Greenbelt Planning: Resettlement Administration Builds Three Model Towns," "Greenbelt Towns: Resettlement Administration," "Greenbelt.", 1936 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Greensboro, North Carolina: "Greensboro Suburban Analysis.", 1956 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Highway Planning: parking problems., 1938, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Highway Users Federation for Safety and Mobility: "Urban Highway Design Teams.", 1970 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Historic Preservation, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Historic Preservation, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Historic Preservation, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Historic Preservation, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii: "Honolulu R/UDAT 1974." (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Warburton, Ralph., 1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Housing and Urban Development: New Towns., 1970-1972 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Housing and Urban Development: 701 Revision., 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Weaver, Robert., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Housing and Urban Development: press release., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Housing and Urban Development: applications, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Division of Land Development., 1967 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Demonstration Cities Program., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Housing and Urban Development: AIA Conferences, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Housing and Urban Development: publications: "Proposed Minimum Standards for Low-Cost Housing and for the Improvement of Existing Substandard Areas.", 1966 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Housing and Urban Development: Open Space, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Industrial Planning, 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Innisfree Foundation, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - International Planning: "Urban Planning in Developing Countries." (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - International Planning: Asia: "Public Administration Problems of New and Rapidly Growing Towns in Asia.", 1960 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - International Planning: Austria., 1956 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - International Planning: Caracas., 1976 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - International Planning: Canada., 1969 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - International Planning: Denmark., 1960 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - International Planning: Egypt: "Restoration Survey Report.", 1966 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - International Planning: England: "The Society for the Protection of Ancient Buildings for the Eighty-Sixth to Eighty-Eighth Year.", 1963 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - International Planning: Germany., 1957 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - International Planning: International Housing Country Report Series: includes reports on Ghana, Ivory Coast, Guatemala, Jordan, Ethiopia., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - International Planning: Israel., 1964 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - International Planning: Israel: "Two Case Studies of Rural Planning and Development in Israel," "Rural Planning in Israel," "Housing Policy in Regions of Rapid Population Growth," "National Planning for the Redistribution of Population and the Establishment of New Towns in Israel," "Shikun Upituah Leisrael.", 1964 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - International Planning: Japan., 1951 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - International Planning: Mexico: 16th International Housing and Town Planning Congress., 1938 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - International Planning: New Zealand: "New Zealand's Experience with Land-Value Taxation.", 1943 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - International Planning: Poland: "Rebirth of a City: The Reconstruction of Warsaw.", 1946 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - International Planning: Tunisia: "Manuel d'Architecture et de Construction en Tunisie.", 1968 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - International Planning: Turkey: "Planning in Turkey," "Planning," "Introducing Turkey's State Planning Organization.", 1963 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Legislation: Florida, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Legislation: Urban Growth and New Community Act of 1970. (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Legislation: Urban and Redevelopment Act of 1969. (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Legislation: Urban and Redevelopment Act., 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Legislation: Federal Highway Act of 1968. (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Legislation: Governmental publications., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Legislation: New Towns., 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 47-48)
    - Legislation: New Towns., 1967-1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Lexington, Kentucky, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Maitland, Florida: "Maitland of Tomorrow.", 1969 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Mapping: "Mapping, Survey and Planning Procedures: Under the New Three Year Budget Plan.", 1928 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Maps: Boston, New York City, Cape Cod., n.d. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Maryland Institute of Art, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Missouri Valley Authority, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Model Inner City Community Organization, Inc., 1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Moore, William, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - National Endowment for the Arts: Hunatech Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - National Housing Agency: Federal Public Housing Authority., 1945 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - National Housing Agency: General., 1944-1946 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - National Park Service, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - New Castle, Indiana: "The Story of a Middle-Western Town which Seeks Not Wider Streets or More Parks or Greater Wealth for their Own Sake, but a Place to Live which Shall Be Safe and Peaceful and Satisfying.", 1944 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - New Communities: Kytle, Jaeger., 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - New Mexico: "A Design for Development Decisions," "State Resources Development Plan," "Rich in Profit Potential," "Projections of the Population of New Mexico and Its Counties to the Year 2000," "New Mexico's Economy in 1964., 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - New Towns Movement, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - New York City: "'Let There Be Commitment," "National Housing Becomes a National Issue," "The Threatened City," "Poverty and Economic Development in New York City.", 1937, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - New York State Historical Association: "NYSHA Selective Reference Guide to Historic Preservation.", 1966 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - North Central Florida Regional Planning Council, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Northwest Regional Council, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Organization for Housing and Community Development, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Pan-American Unit: "Americas United," "A Summary of the Sessions on Employment, Labor, and Trade Relations.", 1943 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Pawtucket, Rhode Island: "Master Plan.", 1965 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Philadelphia: Redevelopment Authority, City of Philadelphia Annual Report; Philadelphia City Planning Commission Annual Report., 1967 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Planning: General, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Portland, Oregon: "Portland Improvement.", 1943 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Project East River: "Reduction of Urban Vulnerability.", 1952 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Project East River: "General Report.", 1952 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Public Affairs pamphlets: "The Races of Mankind," "Restless Americans.", 1936, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Publications and reprints: miscellaneous, 1943-1967 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Railroads: "Facts about the Proposed Merger of the Pennsylvania and New York Central Railroads." (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Reclamation: General., 1945-1948 (Box 43, Folder 33-34)
    - Recreation: National Parks U.S.A., n.d. (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Research, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Research: Opinion Surveys, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Rochester, New York: "Preliminary Report: Phase 1 of the General Neighborhood Renewal Plan for the Rochester Model Neighborhood Area.", 1969 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Rural Taxation: "A Program for the Use of Tax-Abandoned Lands," "Tax Delinquency and Rural Land-Use Adjustment.", 1942 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Saarinen, Eliel: architecture articles, 1931-1932 (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
    - San Francisco: "Blight and Taxes.", 1947 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Connecticut Region: "Opportunities for Historic Preservation.", 1968 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Slum Clearance Plan Under Title 1 of the Housing Act of 1949: Corlears Hook, Fort Greene, Harlem, Lincoln Square, Manhattontown, Morningside Manhattonville, North Harlem, New York University/Bellevue, Pratt Institute Area, Washington Square South, Washington Square Southeast (Box 44, Folder 6-8)
    - Surveys: "An Outline for Making Surveys.", 1944 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee: Housing: "New Homes for Old: Publicly Owned Housing in Tennessee.", 1948 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee: Planning: "Recreation Highways.", 1946 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1937-1945 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Texas: "Postwar Economic Planning Commission," "Manufacturing synthetic fibers, tire cord, textiles, and carpeting in Texas.", 1945, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Texas: Housing, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Town Planning Institute, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Traffic Survey Problems: "The Transportation Problem," "Traffic Improvement Program," "Denver Ordnance Plant Trip Study," "A Traffic Survey [of Chicago]," "Traffic and Residential Real Estate.", 1938-1946 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Transportation, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - United States Forest Service: "A Memorandum on Conservation as One of the Three Elements of National Defense.", 1941 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - University of Denver: "D.U. Plans," "School of Architecture and Planning," "Colorado State Planning and Zoning Acts and Related Legislation," "'You Cannot Have a Great City Without a Great University.", 1946-1949 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - University Facilities Research Center: "Horizontal and Vertical Circulation in University Instructional and Research Buildings," "University Research Buildings for Short-Term Grant Programs.", 1961 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - University of Florida: "Workshop: Architectural Preservation," "Prepared Papers for the First Annual University of Florida Growth Conference.", 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - University of Florida: Urban Studies: "Bibliography of Research and Documents Relating to Gainesville and Alachua County," "Current University of Florida Urban and Regional Research.", 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Unwin Publications: "Town and Country Planning and Land Values," "Housing and Planning," "In the Hampstead Garden Suburb," "Housing and Planning?English and American Compared," "The Garden City Conference at Bournville Report of Proceedings," "Planning and Education," "Housing and Town Planning Lectures 1936-1937," "Nothing Gained by Overcrowding.", 1909-1937 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Urban Observatory Program, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Urban Planning Assistance Program, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Utah: Planning: "Let's Plan Weber County.", 1947 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Virginia: Planning: "Practical Steps in Town Planning.", 1947 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Vollmer Associates: Stolport, 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, 1969-1972 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - West Parish Meetinghouse, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - World War II: "Report on War and Post-War Adjustment Policies," "State Planning and Post-War Planning, City Planning, County Planning, Regional Planning, etc.", 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - World's Fair, New York: Art Guide., 1939 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Oversize (Flat)
    - Sketches, watercolors, The University School News, 1923-1967 (Box 49)
    - Sketches, paintings, memorabilia, 1924-1949 (Box 50)
    - Sketches, photographs, c. 1922 (Box 51)
    - Drawing of village and castle, Undated (Folder 1)
    - Maps and plans, Date unknown (Folder 2-4)
  - Projects, Reference Materials
    - "The Beginnings of Federal Planning Assistance," Journal of the American Planning Association; related notes and correspondence with Raymond J. Burby, editor., 1984 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "The Beginnings of Federal Planning Assistance" revisions and correspondence with Raymond J. Burby., 1984 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - "The Beginnings of Federal Planning Assistance" final copy., 1984 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - "The Beginnings of Federal Planning Assistance" revisions to be typed., 1984 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - "701, Before, During and After" draft., 1984 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - "701, Before, During and After" draft., 1984 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Miscellany correspondence and notes, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Florida: correspondence, 1976-1985 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Florida: Florida North Chapter: American Institute of Architects: correspondence, memoranda, bylaws., 1972-1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Florida: Florida North Chapter: American Institute of Architects: correspondence, "An Environmental Land Planning Study," memoranda, notes, meeting agenda., 1971-1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Florida: Florida North Chapter: American Institute of Architects: slate of nominees, holiday party announcement, meeting notices, list of members, committee appointments, budget proposal, memoranda, correspondence., 1972-1983 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Florida: Mid-Florida Chapter: American Institute of Architects: Charette, correspondence., 1972 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Florida Legislature: "The Local Government Comprehensive Planning Act," correspondence., 1975 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Florida: Growth Policy: Springwater Conference: program; available position announcement; Florida Planning; Checkmates and Challenges Conference; The Monitor; "Notes towards a workshop on Stimulating Employment Through Neighborhood Revitalization.", 1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Florida Planning and Zoning Association: South Florida Chapter: Overview; correspondence, bylaws, membership rosters, FPZA Conference program, Annual Workshop program, registration form, memoranda, "Commercial Revitalization Program.", 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 8)